我没偷懒
I'm not slacking.
你就这么跟指导员说话的吗
Is that how you talk to your drill instructor?
报告长官  我没偷懒
Sir, I'm not slacking.
你站好了  看着我的眼睛
You stand up. You look me in the eye!
我很难受  我不行了
I feel lousy. I can't.
这里没有"不行"两个字
"Can't" doesn't exist here!
现在  你要么完成这次训练
Now, you finish this course,
要么今天被关小黑屋  听明白了吗
or you're in isolation the rest of the day, you hear me?
麦克唐纳  准备好让帕克斯吃土了吗
Macdonald, you ready to make Parks eat your dust?
-是的  长官  -预备  冲
- Sir, yes, sir! - Ready, go!
你耳朵聋了吗  我说了冲  冲
Are your ears malfunctioning? I said go! Go!
冲  趴下  趴下
Go! Get down! Get down!
腰沉下去
Belly down!
Belly down.
动起来
Move it!
爬上去  加把劲
Get up on there. You've gotta push.
快点  不许掉下来
Move it. Don't you dare fall.
抓住栏杆  抓牢了
Grab the bars. Grab there!
快点  快点  膝盖抬起来
Move it! Move it! Knees up.
膝盖抬起来  快  快
Knees up! Move! Move!
到墙那去  冲到墙那去
Find the wall! Hit that wall! Hit that wall!
快点  爬上去
Move it. Get up on there.
别掉下来  速度  往上爬
Don't you fall on me. Faster! Move it!
你怎么了  帕克斯
What's the matter, Parks?
受伤了吗
You got a boo boo?
报告长官  我在流血
Sir, I'm bleeding, sir.
-生命危急吗  -不
- Is your life in immediate danger? - No.
那就给我想办法翻过这面墙
Then you get your ass up over that wall!
我说  把你的屁股弄到  啊
I said get your ass over the--gaaa!
怎么了
What's going on?
我背疼
My back hurts.
我不能动了
I can't move.
帮帮我  我站不起来
Help. Help. I can't get up.
这里没有"不行"两个字
"Can't" doesn't exist here.
我们不该看这个的
We should not be looking at this.
他发了个提醒
He sent out an alert.
不看也太不给面子了
It would be rude not to look.
虽然我看得眼睛都酸了
Though I am straining my eyes.
有什么可看的吗
What are we checking out?
你的个人主页
Your profile page.
什么  我没有
Why? I haven't--
那...不是我
That...is not me.
那就是你
That is you.
人是我  不过那个可不是
That's me, but that is not.
有人把它变小了
Whoever did this made it smaller.
小了不是一星半点
Much, much smaller.
这人还挺爱挑你毛病
Whoever did this has a bone to pick with you.
讽刺的是  你的
Ironic, since your bone is--
根本就没在那图上
Is not in that picture.
我现在就可以证明  你真的想看吗
My proof is right here. You really want to see it?
算了  我信你
Oh, whoa. Convinced.
知道是谁干的吗
You have any idea who did this?
我甚至不知道原始图片是哪来的
I don't even know where the original picture is from.
卡尔顿宾馆的洗手间
The bathroom at the Carlton hotel.
浴巾  上面有宾馆的标记
The towel. Hotel logo's reversed.
应该是从镜子里拍的
Shot must have been taken in the mirror.
我们去那参加了桑福德·威尔斯的婚礼
We were there for Sanford Wells' wedding.
这倒是能缩小范围
That must narrow it down.
他在那儿睡了三个女人
He slept with three women there.
原来你是牛郎
Oh, you're a whore.
38岁的前海军陆战队员
38-year-old former marine
背疼来看急诊
came into the E.R. with back pain.
现在他的膀胱和背一样疼了
Now his bladder aches as much as his back
因为他没办法排尿
because he can't empty it.
今早有啥有趣的吗
What are we looking at this morning?
名流走光
Up-skirt celebrity?
还是小萌猫
Endearingly funny cat?
有项关于同性恋更能胜任家长的研究
Another study about gays being better parents.
我们被"拉拉"字样吸引了
We were lured in by the word "Lesbian."
他服用过抗组织胺或抗胆碱能类药物吗
Has he taken any antihistamines or anticholinergics?
没  急救室还排除了前列腺肥大
Nope. And the E.R. ruled out enlarged prostate,
大肠蠕动停止以及脊椎损伤
stopped colon, and spinal injury.
拥有参军背景
Military history--
保持了与年龄不符的好体型
in suspiciously good shape for his age.
干着吓唬孩子的工作
Makes a living bullying kids.
我想会不会是  滥用类固醇
I'm thinking...steroids?
太有趣了
Fascinating.
谢谢  我们可以使他摆脱
Thanks. We can wean him off--
不是滥用类固醇有趣  那蠢透了
Steroids isn't fascinating, it's moronic.
没有症状表明他激素失调
There's no other sign of hormonal imbalance.
有趣的是你把训练和吓唬
What's fascinating is that you equate
划了等号
discipline with bullying.
就是说你父母要么经常训练你
which means that your parents either disciplined you
要么没怎么训过你  我估计是没怎么训过
too much or too little-- I'm guessing too little.
你认同病人的人生观
It's hardly surprising
真是一点也不奇怪
you agree with our patient's philosophy.
你把自己的部门搞得跟新兵训练营一样
You run your department like a boot camp.
就好像残忍能确保好表现一样
As if cruelty ensures performance.
轮到我反驳你了吗
Oh, is this where I'm supposed to disagree with you?
尿潴留一般都是由
The diagnosis of urinary retention depends on
特定的机制引起的
the particular mechanical cause.
我们得知道究竟是尿路阻塞
We need to know if there's a blockage in the urethra
还是膀胱神经或肌肉的问题
versus a nerve or a muscle problem with the bladder.
有意思  别无他指
Fascinating... without misdirect.
给他导尿  看看是什么
Cath him and see what's stopping him
阻止他排尿的
from emptying his bilge.
不是你  奇斯
Oh, not you, Chase.
让牙签船长去面对
Sending Captain Micropenis to deal with
正常尺寸的家伙
what is probably normal-sized equipment,
即使是我也不能这么残忍
it's too cruel, even for me.
早上好
Good morning.
什么风把小卡迪吹到这来了
And what brings the lesser Cuddy to these parts?
我跟儿科医生约了打疫苗
Pediatrician appointment for an s-h-o-t.
瓦尔登伍德要求申请时提交
Waldenwood insists vaccination reports
接种报告
go in with the application.
宝贝  把麦片吃完
Honey, finish your oatmeal.
瓦尔登伍德  不会凑巧是个寄宿学校
Waldenwood. Is that by any chance a boarding school
或者劳动夏令营吧
or a work camp?
是我们的首选幼儿园
It's our first-choice preschool.
金砖铺地
Blocks made of gold...
孩子们都不用自己挖鼻子
kids don't have to pick their own noses...
顶级的设施  一流的教师
Great facilities and teachers.
还有著名的天才班
And they're known for their gifted program.
你确定那地方适合她吗
You sure that's the right place for her?
听上去有点虚荣
Sounds a little snobby.
我做过调查  也去看过了
I've done my research. We visited.
那地方绝对合适
It's a perfect fit.
你会感到有些胀
You'll feel pressure.
憋到不能再忍了
I need you to tell us
告诉我们
when the urge to void becomes unbearable.
好的
Mm-hmm.
抱歉了  凡事
Sorry, can't make you feel better
都得先苦后甜
till we make you feel worse.
我明白
I get it.
和我平时干的一样
Goes for what I do too.
我们只在必要的时候制造痛苦
We cause pain when it's the only option.
我在训练营里训练的孩子们
The kids I work with at the camp are there
是一个法官送来的
because a judge sent them.
他们不先改掉坏习惯
I can't teach them good behaviors
我就没法规范纪律作风
without first getting rid of all their bad ones.
我不够强硬他们就不学好
That's not gonna happen unless I push them.
我不明白  为什么态度强硬
I don't see why metaphorical pushing
总要演变成动真格
has to involve actual pushing.
可能我训练得狠了点  但我从不打他们
I may work these kids hard, but I never hit them.
你逼他们趴在地上前进
You march them into the ground
比打他们还严重
instead of knocking them there.
没错  但这没得选
Yeah, well, it beats the alternatives,
否则他们最后不是进监狱就是入黑帮
which is ending up in jail or in a gang or...
要么进棺材
a coffin.
你一般能教好多少
How often do you pull that off?
三分之二不会再犯
Two-thirds never re-offend.
比少管所的数字要乐观
That's better numbers than juvie.
她很聪明  但还嫩点
She's brilliant, but new to the real world.
没错  医生  我要尿了
Yeah. Hey, doc, I gotta go.
我们帮你排尿
Let's empty you out.
把尿液给陶博
Take this urine to Taub.
让他镜下找一找细菌
Have him screen it for bacteria.
我会分析数据
I'll analyze this data.
打了半小时电话  没用
Half hour on the phone, no go.
网站不肯撤掉那些图片
Website won't take down the picture.
我以为他们禁止粗俗图片的
I thought their policy doesn't allow nude photos.
现在  在桌上轻敲试管
Now tap the tube gently against the table
让细胞悬浮起来
To re-suspend the cells.
确实是这么规定的
They don't.
但技术上讲  我不再那么粗俗了
Technically... I'm no longer nude.
也许你可以注销掉你的账号
Maybe you should shut down your account.
我试过了  但不知道谁改了我的密码
I tried, but whoever did this changed my password,
所以我根本不能证明那是我的主页
so I can't even prove it's my page.
这是个线索  她是个黑客
Well, there's a clue. She's got serious text skills.
我的密码就是"密码"这俩字
My password was "Password."
你真是个白痴牛郎
You're a dumb whore.
三个里面哪个像是有嫌疑的呢
Do any of the three seem like a more likely suspect?
可能是其中一个上传的
Maybe one was clingier?
我都记不起她们的名字了
I don't even remember their names.
听着  现在对我来说是个非常时期
Listen, this is a tough time for me.
和瑞秋分手  搬进旅馆住
Breaking up with rachel, moving into a hotel.
你要知道  你的糗事
I want you to know how much your humiliation
减轻了我多少负担啊
has eased my burden.
尿液里没有细菌
Urine is clean for bacteria.
没什么意外  因为他的膀胱检查显示
Not surprising, since his bladder tests show
他的疼痛其实是神经问题
that his pain problem is really a nerve problem.
神经性膀胱功能障碍
Neurogenic bladder.
可能是脊髓肿瘤  大脑性麻痹引起的
Could mean spinal cord tumor, cerebral palsy.
要是豪斯就会定义成梅毒
House is gonna go right for syphilis.
他凭什么这么肯定
How can he be so sure?
尴尬的病情造成罕见的并发症
Rare complication of an embarrassing illness.
正是豪斯的菜
It's practically a House special.
我想先他一步
I want to get ahead.
检查他的血液有没有梅毒病菌
Let's go test his blood for syphilis.
好的  我要取些血样
Okay, I'm gonna take some blood.
就疼一小下  准备好了吗
This will only hurt for a second. Ready?
住手  别杀我
Stop it! Stop trying to kill me.
-放开她  -这女孩想要杀我
- Hey, let her go.  - That girl was trying to kill me!
放她走
Let her go.
保安  这里需要人帮忙
Security, get some help in here!
放开我  放开我
Let me go. Let me go!
她没事的  我们继续讨论病人的情况吧
She's fine. How 'bout we get back to someone who isn't?
病人已经被关禁闭  并在用氟哌啶醇
The patient's in restraints and on haldol,
貌似能让他清醒些
which seems to have made him lucid.
临床鉴别诊断
Differential diagnosis.
背部疼痛  神经性膀胱功能障碍  精神病
Back pain, neurogenic bladder, psychosis.
我快被掐死才诊断出的症状
A symptom which we learned about when he choked me.
怎么早没看出来
Hate to slow us down by acknowledging it.
现在你看出来了吧
And yet you have.
符合三期梅毒症状
Tertiary syphilis fits.
检查梅毒病菌呈阴性
The tests came back negative.
一些药物可能引起那些症状
Several meds could cause those symptoms.
三环抗抑郁药  利他林
Tricyclic antidepressants, ritalin.
一些原生植物也可以
Also other native plants.
苦艾  曼陀罗
Wormwood, jimson weed.
那他肯定吃过大量曼陀罗种子或者利他林
The amount of jimson weed or ritalin he'd have to ingest,
但如果是这样的话  他应该会提起的
seems like he would have mentioned it.
除非他不知道
Unless he didn't know about it.
也许是训练营的孩子们
Maybe one of those kids at the camp
厌烦了魔鬼训练  给他下了药
got tired of driscoll's lessons and poisoned him.
去营地
Go to the camp.
去查查可能的毒药
Check for potential poisons.
我通常会否决你所有的建议
I all but ignored your assault,
让你知道这里没有所谓的同情
showed you no compassion whatsoever,
但你提了个好建议
but you came up with a good idea.
给你加一分  打是情骂是爱
Score one for tough love.
很高兴听说你找到心上人了
Glad to hear you met someone you like.
婚姻是最好的解决方式
Weddings are good for that.
我是想保持联系的
I was hoping to get in touch.
但实际上  我对名字不太敏感
The thing is, I'm a bit fuzzy on names.
抱歉  在婚礼的免费酒吧里
Sorry. Open bar.
她当时坐在辛普森大夫那一桌
She was sitting at Dr. Simpson's table.
深色皮肤  紫色连衣裙  胸口很低
Brunette, purple dress, low-cut.
那是我侄女  韦恩·菲利普斯
That my niece, Winn Phillips.
您侄女
Your niece?
真不可思议
Fantastic.
她的信息在你邮箱里了
Her info is in your email.
还有  一个金发女郎
Also, there was a blonde.
穿绿色连衣裙
Green dress.
你想让我帮你钓两个马子?
You want me to hook you up with two women?
实际上  是三个
Actually, three.
没有考试
How do you cheat on a test
你还要怎么作弊
when there's no test?
抱歉  我不陪你玩
Sorry, not playing.
走开  豪斯
Go away, house.
我不要再给你提建议了
I am not giving you advice
否则你会歪曲原意
just so you can distort it
迎合自我
to suit your own warped world view.
但我们向来合作愉快
But it's been working so well.
卡迪想让瑞秋进沃登伍德幼儿园
Cuddy wants to get Rachel into Waldenwood preschool.
问题是  瑞秋比猪还笨
The problem is, Rachel's dumber than a paste sandwich.
她进不去让你很困扰
And her not getting in bothers you.
你很关心瑞秋  这不是建议
You care about Rachel. That was not advice.
卡迪关心她
Cuddy cares about her.
要是瑞秋被拒绝入园  卡迪会伤心的
When Rachel gets rejected, Cuddy will be upset.
所以身为男友  她会希望我
And as the boyfriend, I will be expected
安慰她和支持她
to be supportive and consoling.
这不是你的强项  我奉劝你
Not your strengths, I grant you.
别管这事
Leave it alone.
这不过是亲子活动  没事的
It's just a play date. It'll be fine.
这种亲自活动
Play date being their code for
是他们用来淘汰笨猪的伎俩
way to weed out the paste sandwiches.
他们会让她做智力和算术游戏
They'll hand her puzzles and counting games,
而瑞秋会坐在那吃积木
and Rachel will just sit there and eat the pieces.
糟糕  真糟糕  我真是个白痴
Oh, crap! Crap! I'm such a sucker!
谢谢你的建议
Thanks for the advice.
就是这个与世隔绝的地方
That's the isolation area.
行为有问题的小孩被送到这里
Kids who've behaved badly go there,
有时都没的休息
sometimes 23 hours a day.
好像确实能激励良好表现
Sound like a pretty good incentive to behave.
治标不治本
Yeah, by treating the symptom instead of the disease.
基础理论认为
Basic systems theory.
问题少年都是问题家庭的产物
Troubled kids are produced by troubled families.
这地方根本没把目标放在
This place doesn't even attempt to change the environment
改变毁掉他们的生活环境上
that damaged them in the first place.
世上无不是的孩子  只有不是的父母咯
So there are no bad kids, only bad parents?
那为什么我弟弟成了前科犯
Then why is my brother an ex-con?
善待孩子  但也要因材施教
Treating kids decently doesn't mean identically.
有些孩子需要更多的纪律监督
Some kids need more structure or discipline.
没人需要这种地方
Nobody needs this place.
或许我们找错了方向
Maybe we're coming at this wrong.
找到投毒者
We find a poisoner,
从他身上找毒素的线索
and let them point us toward the poison.
德里斯科尔的队里有24个孩子
Driscoll's got 24 kids in his troop.
你想跟每个孩子谈一遍吗
You want to interview all of them?
或许不需要每个孩子都谈
Maybe we don't need to.
德里斯科尔总关我禁闭
Driscoll sent me to isolation all the time.
但是我没有给他下毒
It doesn't mean I poisoned him.
他是疯子  我又不是
He's the psycho, not me.
说句话
Tell 'em.
D.I.德里斯科尔对他比我们其他人更为严厉
D.I. Driscoll's way harder on him than the rest of us.
说不定是因为他比谁都能惹刺
Maybe because he's a bigger pain in the ass.
你是怎么进来的
What are you in here for?
从商店偷东西
Shoplifting.
你想让罪名升级为二级谋杀吗
You ready to upgrade to second-degree murder?
进监狱蹲十年
Spend ten years in jail?
如果他死于你投的毒
If he dies because of whatever you gave him,
这就是你的下场
that's what'll happen.
那有什么可怕
That supposed to scare me?
我妈死了  我从小没见过我爸
My mom's dead, my dad's never been around.
从这儿出去  我会被转到另一个寄养家庭
And after this, I'll get bounced to another foster home.
反正也是前途无亮
My future's not exactly bright.
坐牢不过是早晚的事
Prison now or later
我也不在乎
doesn't make that much of a difference to me.
我说  你还拖不拖地板了
Dude, I'm not mopping the whole floor by myself.
你的眼睛红了
Your eyes are red.
可能是对洗涤液过敏
Might be an allergic reaction to the cleaning solution.
我有过敏症
It's just my allergies.
你吃抗过敏药吗
Do you take anything for them?
现在没有
Not right now.
为什么不吃
Why not?
静脉注射液会助你将毒素排出体外
These IV fluids will help flush the drugs out of your system.
你们知道是哪个孩子给我投毒的了吗
You know which of the kids dosed me?
这事不关系到治疗
It's not medically relevant.
我不会伤害他的
Look, I'm not gonna hurt him.
我知道你为什么怕我
But I get why you're scared of me.
今天上午的事我非常抱歉
I'm real sorry about this morning.
没必要道歉  你是病人
No apology necessary. You're ill.
你当时不知道自己在做什么
You didn't know what you were doing.
我错过也迷茫过
I used to be a real screwup.
军队教我相信
The military taught me that
一切行为必有后果
actions always have consequences.
身为男子汉就要勇于承担后果
Part of being a man is accepting them.
我也是这样教那些孩子的
And after all the times I've said that to the kids,
我一定要道歉
an apology is necessary.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我的心跳很快
My heart's kinda racing.
我来
I got it.
心率170  便携式心电监测
Heart rate is 170. P.A.T.
必须减缓心跳直到平稳
Until proven otherwise, we've gotta slow it down.
6毫克腺苷  快速静脉推注
Six milligrams adenosine, IV bolus.
叫护士推急救车进来
Tell the nurse to get in here with the crash cart.
静脉滴注导致他心率飙升
Pushing fluid sent his heart into overdrive.
用了三剂腺苷才控制住
It took three doses of adenosine to get it under control.
抗组织胺药物毒性治疗后
Treating him for antihistamine toxicity
出现新症状  说明
revealed a new symptom, which revealed that
他根本没有抗组织胺药物中毒
he didn't have antihistamine toxicity in the first place.
豪斯  你在哪儿
House, where are you?
儿童乐园  钓小宝贝的好地方
Playground. Great place to meet chicks.
还有孩子妈妈
Their moms too.
心动过速可能是体液免疫反应
Tachycardia could be a humoral effect--
肥大细胞增多症
mastocytosis.
该有其他肠道或者皮肤症状
We'd see other GI or cutaneous symptoms.
胰腺胰岛细胞瘤
Pancreatic insulinoma.
该会引发膀胱疾病
It would cause bladder problems,
嗜铬细胞瘤则不然
unlike pheochromocytoma.
说得好  奇斯
Well done, Chase.
现在  把手机关了
Now, turn off your phone.
你听到了  开着震动呢
You heard that? It's on vibrate.
我猜你的手机已经被打爆了
I'm assuming it's been ringing
因为你的Facebook状态改成了
almost nonstop since you changed your status update
"只为大块头女士心动
to "Nothing lights my fire like a lady of size--
"三百磅以下勿扰"
less than three bills, don't bother calling."
后面还有你的手机号
Followed by your cell number.
别生气  我们不该笑你
No, no, no, you're right.
这事既不聪明也不搞笑
This is in no way clever and hysterical.
在你跟胖妞翻云覆雨前
Before you start rolling anyone in flour,
先检查病人有无嗜铬细胞瘤
work the patient out for a pheo.
做垂体肾上腺系统扫描  收集24小时尿液
Adrenaline pituitary scans, 24-hour urine collection.
孩子是招生会后
How soon after the admissions session
多久发病的
did the child get sick?
孩子刚刚到家就突然发病
The kid barely got home before she collapsed.
家长已经急疯了  急需知道病因
Her parents are a wreck. Desperate for answers.
你身上有没有出现什么症状
Have you experienced any symptoms,
还有没有其他人参与组织招生会
or does someone else oversee these sessions?
有几名教师在旁监督
The teachers supervise.
没听说有人感到不适
No one's mentioned feeling sick.
我很愿意打电话给孩子家长提供帮助
I'd love to call the family and offer my support.
抱歉  我不能透露姓名
Sorry, I can't reveal names.
医患保密协议
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
招生会的游戏活动都在这里进行吗
So this is where all the admissions play dates happen?
她当时不会在其它房间吧
She wouldn't have been in another room?
所有孩子都在这里活动
This is where we have them all.
为安全起见  我们或许该把这些玩具处理掉
Maybe, to be safe, we get rid of these toys.
别别  不要扔
No, no, no, don't do that.
测到有毒物质我会告诉你的
I'll tell you if anything's toxic.
目前你只要尽量减少暴露就好
For now, you should minimize your exposure.
应该有人监督我
I'm supposed to be supervised.
扫描程序是编好的
The scan is pre-programmed.
病人没有任何风险
There's no risk to the patient.
你就坐在这里  看着监视器
You're literally gonna sit here, watch the monitor,
如果他感觉孤单了就陪他说句话
And chat with him if he gets lonely.
可是
Uh...still.
回来向我汇报
Report me.
你感觉怎么样
How you doing in there?
你用不着在我面前保护兰德勒
You shouldn't bother trying to protect Landon.
我知道是他给我下的毒
I know he's the one who drugged me.
抗组胺药不是你的病因
The antihistamines aren't what got you sick.
那也改变不了他投毒的事实
Doesn't change the fact that he did it.
在他身上我什么方法都试过了  可还是
I tried everything with that kid. I just...
没什么进展
can't break through.
你很关心他
It's clear you care about him.
你有没有试着告诉他这点
Have you tried telling him that?
有些事你得明白
You gotta understand something.
这些孩子  都是见人下菜碟的好手
These kids, they're all manipulators.
我虽然关心他们
As much as I care about all of them,
我不能  我不能表露出来
I can't-- I can't show them that
除非我们能互相尊重
unless there's some mutual respect.
-否则  -先不论其他的孩子
- otherwise-- - Forget those other kids.
就说说这个
Think about this kid.
他亲眼目睹自己的母亲得病死去
He watched his mother get sick and die.
又从没见过自己的父亲
He's never known his dad.
谁知道他有多久
Who knows how long it's been
没被人真正关心过了
since anyone's taken care of him,
或者是否有人曾在他身边
or if there's ever been a man around
稍稍待过一段时间
with any degree of consistency?
我相信你是为他好
I believe that you're on his side.
我敢打赌如果让他知道  效果会更好
I'm betting it would help if he did.
你真是个美男子  我可以走了吗
You are a beautiful man. Can I leave now?
我知道这三个女人都在哪儿了
I know where all three women are,
但我不想怪错人
but I'd like to avoid the additional humiliation
以免不必要地丢人现眼
of falsely accusing any of them.
你从这张照片上看出了是哪家旅馆
You I.D. the hotel off this.
但愿你还能找到一些别的线索
I'm hoping there's another clue in there somewhere.
我们可以提高画质
We could enhance the image.
也许她的脸蛋
Maybe her face
能从你光洁可鉴的屁股上映出来
is reflected in that gleam off your butt cheek.
或者也许是时候该让你记住
Or maybe it's time to chalk this up
当一名花花公子的教训了
to the hazards of being a player.
你还不是因为采花成性搅黄了婚姻
Your zipper problems just blew up your marriage.
别动
Don't move.
不像我  你至少没背叛过别人
Unlike me, you've had the decency not to cheat on anyone,
但你根本不在意
but you haven't been giving much thought
这些女人是谁  也没顾及人家的感受
to who these women are, how they might feel.
显而易见  你伤了其中一个的心
Obviously, you hurt one of them.
感情上  你伤了她
Emotionally, you hurt her,
肉体上  你怎么会知道呢
because physically, how would you even know?
看来你那根小牙签还真挺纤细的
Looks like your shorty is a shorty.
你来早了  晚饭还没好呢
You're early. Dinner's not ready.
没事
Oh...okay.
我陪瑞秋去她房间里玩一会儿
Rachel and I will go play in her room.
真的
Really?
我饿了  快烧饭去
I'm hungry. Go cook.
好吧  你个小木头人
All right, you little lump of clay...
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel. Rachel...
这是个新玩具
It's a new toy.
哪个小孩不喜欢新玩具
What kid doesn't like new toys?
低能儿才不喜欢吧
A moron, that's who.
看呀  这么多漂亮颜色
Okay, look at the pretty colors.
这是什么颜色呀
Now, what color is this?
橙色
Orange.
没错  那是橙色  这个呢
Yes, that is orange. What color is this?
好啦  不玩积木了  积木再见
Okay, blocks going away. Bye-bye blocks.
下次要把堤坝加固哦
Next time, reinforce the levees.
什么陆军工兵呀  太差劲了
Bad corps of army engineers. Bad!
这是什么
What's this?
是小环子
Rings!
看看这些小环子
Look at the rings.
这个游戏的目标是
Now, the goal of this game is...
忍着别杀了你
to not kill you.
哪阵风把你吹来了
Why are you here?
等等  你是不是把性病传染给我了
Wait, did you give me an STD?
不  我没有  别转移话题
No, I did not. Don't deflect.
这张照片是你这个身高的人拍的
That picture was taken by someone your height.
-赶紧把它撤了  -什么照片
- Just take it down. - What picture?
好吧  你自己看看
Fine. Play it that way.
这么说
So, uh...
你真的很喜欢小猫  是吧
You really like kittens, huh?
当然  你说过你也很喜欢的
Yeah. You said you did too.
难怪你会生气呢
No wonder you're pissed.
这的确不是你  不过我没可没拍
'cause that is not you. And I didn't take it.
你是说我光脚还是穿高跟鞋的身高
Did you mean my height with heels or without?
咱们在房里的时候你又没穿高跟鞋
You weren't wearing heels when we were in that room--
哦对了  你穿着
Oh, yes, you were.
我正准备脱掉的时候
I started to take them off,
是你求我别脱的
and then you asked me very nicely not to.
况且我为什么要这么做
Why would I do this?
我是说  这事儿我又不生你气
I mean, I'm not mad about what happened with us.
或者可以说不生你
Or apparently with you
和婚礼上其他女人的气
and any other woman at that wedding.
不好意思  我猜我的法医鉴定师
Sorry, I guess my forensic analysis
没我想象的那么好
wasn't as advanced as I thought.
等等  你不用走那么急吧
Wait. You know, you don't have to rush off.
高跟鞋我还留着呢
I still have those heels.
满眼都是布面塞绒的玩具动物
Everywhere you looked, gingham and stuffed animals.
你怎么从那儿逃出来的
How did you get out of there?
我没有  马上出来
I didn't... right away.
她生理上没什么问题
Wasn't anything wrong with her physically.
排除一个了  还有三人行中的两位
One down, two members of the threesome to go.
你可以扔套套决定了
You should flip a condom to choose.
我们查了他的肾上腺  垂体和甲状腺
We checked his adrenal, pituitary, and thyroid glands.
检测了他体内的儿茶酚胺
Monitored his catecholamines.
不是嗜铬细胞瘤
It's not a pheo.
我们得给他输地尔硫卓来调节心率
We had to put him on a diltiazem drip to regulate his heart.
那就意味着他快没时间了
That means he's running out of time.
说明你也快了
It means you are too.
你努力软化他
Your campaign to soften him up
让他对孩子宽容一点
so he would go easier on the kids...
做尽无用功来证明你自己的成长方式
All in a pointless attempt to validate your own upbringing.
又心律失常了
Another cardiac arrhythmia?
不是我们的病人
Not our patient.
是急诊室传呼
It's the E.R.
豪斯接手的
That patient House admitted
那个背痛和尿潴留的病人...
with back pain and urinary retention...
再来一个配成对怎么样
How do you feel about a matched set?
我们要追查你们共同接触过的物品
We need to track your common exposures.
你们用什么洗发水
What shampoo do you use?
训练营给什么就用什么
Whatever crap the camp gives us.
我也是
Same here.
我们要知道只有你们用过的东西
We need things exclusive to you,
而不是整个训练营共用的
but not the rest of the camp.
否则  生病的人就多了去了
Otherwise, a lot more people would be sick.
牙膏  止汗体香
Toothpaste, deodorant.
绝对不会是止汗体香让他病倒的
Can't be deodorant making him sick.
他从来不喷  闻起来跟什么似的
He doesn't wear any. Smells like a--
帕克  闭嘴
Park, shut your mouth.
在这儿你又不是我的教官
You're not my drill instructor in here, okay?
那你也不能这么无礼
Doesn't mean you get to be disrespectful.
老子想做什么就做什么
I can do whatever the hell I want.
你管不着
You're not in charge.
他俩肯定有什么联系
There's gotta be a link.
饮食  性生活史  药物滥用
Diet, sexual history, drug abuse.
都不是  相信我  我问过了
No. Believe me, I asked.
那对话真叫一个带劲
Those were some fun conversations.
他俩说的你信吗
Do you believe the answers?
我知道一般都应该说不的
I know the answer to that is always supposed to be no,
但我信
but I did.
这孩子近来被管教得不松
Not like the kid has had much unsupervised time lately.
罗伯特·奇斯医生的快递
Delivery for Dr. Robert Chase.
我就是
That's me.
训练营在丛林里
The camp is in the woods.
感染的机会太多了
There are tons of opportunities for infection
不是每个人都会感染
That not every person will pick up.
水中的军团菌
Legionelosis from water,
灰尘中的弓形虫
Toxoplasmosis from dirt,
还有动物携带的布氏杆菌
Brucellosis fromanimals.
没有一样可以解释他的症状
Too bad none of those explain hissymptoms.
凯西和桑福德·威尔斯感谢我
Casey and Sanford Wells thank me for my extraordinarily
对他们婚礼慈善的慷慨捐赠
generous donation to their wedding charity.
她肯定知道了我的信用卡密码
She must have gotten access to my credit card.
诺卡氏菌属符合
Nocardia fits.
细菌生活在灰尘里  他们都
Bacteria lives in the dirt. They both
诺卡氏菌属感染肺部  而不是膀胱
Nocardia starts in the lungs, not the bladder
多慷慨才称得上非常慷慨
How generous is extraordinarily generous?
打电话给慈善机构
Call the charity.
告诉他们那笔捐赠是诈骗
Explain the donation is a fraud.
再要回威尔斯的新婚礼物吗
And take back Wells' wedding gift?
你也太小气了
You are extraordinarily screwed.
灌木丛是扁虱的天堂
Bushes can make a happy hunting ground for ticks,
莱姆病
lyme disease.
两个病人都没有皮疹或蜱螫伤
Neither of our patients have a rash or tick bite.
40%的莱姆病人都没有皮疹
40% of lyme patients don't develop a rash,
叮伤也很容易被忽略
and a bite is easy to miss.
给他用强力霉素治疗莱姆病
Start him on doxycycline for lyme.
2500美元
$2,500?
注销信用卡  找到那女孩
Cancel your credit card, find that girl,
然后娶了她
and marry her.
倒回去  是泽西海岸
Go back. That was Jersey shore.
我不看垃圾节目
I'm not watching that crap.
不  让他做你的小白鼠吧
No, let him be your guinea pig.
等你确定没问题了再给我服用吧
You can dose me after you're sure you're right.
这药的副作用非常小
The side effects are fairly limited.
而且最好在你发生其他症状之前
And it would be better to treat you
就开始服用它
before you develop any more symptoms.
我想等等看
I want to wait.
我不是你的教员
I'm not your drill instructor.
也没想要打垮你
Not trying to break you.
我唯一的工作就是让你好起来
My only job is to make you better.
这药是我们的最佳选择
I truly believe this medicine is our best shot.
但是吃不吃由你自己决定
But whether or not you take it is up to you.
还有其他要帮忙的吗
Is there anything else I can do for you?
如果你不介意的话  我想再要一个枕头
Another pillow would be cool, if you don't mind.
你看吧
Your turn to pick.
准备  就绪  喂猴子喽
Ready, set, feed the monkey!
这也太奇怪了吧
Well, this isn't weird at all.
她现在是带着微波手套的
She's got the fine motor skills of the hulk
绿巨人
in oven mitts.
你想要涂鸦吗  想不想要
Do you want a doodle? Do you?
喂猴子喽
Feed the monkey.
卡迪每天让她7:30上床
Cuddy puts her to bed at 7:30
这打断了我们的训练时间
which cuts way into our training time.
亲子游戏在星期五
Play date's on friday.
那是什么
What is that?
训狗响片
Dog training clicker.
是连接期望行为和结果之间
Gives immediate positive reinforcement
宝贵几秒的
bridging the precious seconds
正面鼓励
between desired behavior and treat delivery.
豪斯  她又不是小狗
House, she's not a dog.
不过看起来很管用啊
It really seems to be working.
卡迪知道瑞秋在这儿
Does Cuddy know that Rachel's here
被你训练成雪纳瑞吗
and that you're turning her into a schnauzer?
我告诉玛丽娜我和瑞秋正在
I told Marina that Rachel and I
为她妈妈准备一个秘密艺术项目
are working on a secret art project for mommy.
就是说某个足病人
Which means that some pedes patient
会成为艺术项目
is about to be short one art project.
这就是我们为儿童教育作出的牺牲
The sacrifices we make for our children's education.
谁是好女孩  谁是好女孩
Who's a good girl? Who's a good girl?
一定是你
It had to be you.
我给你我的信用卡去买饮料
I gave you my credit card to pay for drinks.
我还给你了
And I gave it back.
我也没有拍照  你可以走了
I didn't take the picture. Now go away.
原谅我不相信你
Well, forgive me if I'm not convinced.
很明显你在生我的气
You're obviously pissed at me.
因为我以为我们已经有关系了
Because I thought we totally had a connection.
而你却没有问我要电话  我
And then when you didn't ask me for my number, I
关系  我们是三个人
A connection? It was a threesome.
是的  但比起妮卡
Yeah, but you were obviously more into me
你明显跟我更亲密啊
than you were into Nika
肯齐  亲爱的  你的电话
Kenzie, honey, you have a phone call.
马上  爸爸
Just a minute, dad.
我在她面前什么都不想说
I didn't want to say anything in front of her,
但你可能说了
but you could have.
你还和你父母一起住吗
You live with your parents?
只是毕业前
Just until graduation.
大学毕业
College?
你多大了
How old are you?
下个月就18了
18...next month.
放松点  又不是犯法什么的
Relax, it's not illegal or anything.
听着  我希望到此为止
Look, I just need this to stop.
你不是早就放弃了吗
Would you give it up already?
我告诉你了  不是我
I told you, it's not me.
我爸妈甚至都不让我上社交网站
My parents won't even let me on social networking sites.
坏人太多了
Too many sexual predators.
拦住他
Stop him.
你要去哪里
Hey, hey. Where you going?
你在生病
Hey, you're sick.
要呆在医院里
You need to be in the hospital.
医院多的是
There's a million hospitals.
而且不会送我会营地
Ones that won't send me back to that camp!
兰德勒  怎么回事
Landon, what's going on?
求你了  别送我回营地
Please, help me. Don't send me back.
这是我的车钥匙  你从我口袋里偷的吗
Those are my car keys. You stole them out of my pocket?
没有不是的孩子对吧
No bad kids, huh?
你们拦住兰德勒了吗
Did you stop Landon?
是的  你怎么样
Yeah, yeah. What's wrong?
我的腿  好疼  好像肌肉夹在虎钳里
Oh, my legs, they hurt. The muscles are in a vise.
什么意思
What does it mean?
还不确定
I'm not sure yet.
10毫克安定  钾40
Ten diazepam. 40 potassium.
肾功能障碍
The leg pain was caused
造成的低钠血症
by a muscle cramp from low sodium,
引起肌肉筋挛进而导致腿痛
which was caused by kidney dysfunction.
兰德勒对强力霉素也没有反应
Landon didn't respond to doxycycline either.
所以可以排除莱姆病了
I think we can rule out lyme.
我以为我已经和他沟通好了
I thought I was getting through to him,
原来他只是想偷我的钥匙
and he just wanted to steal my car keys.
如果只是他先前的行为
If only his previous behavior
就给你借口让你这么想
had given you a reason to expect that.
你为什么要把辣酱涂在玩具上
Why are you putting hot sauce on a toy?
可能你不关心小孩
Maybe you don't care if children chew
咬你的毛毛虫  我觉得是错的
on your caterpillar. I think it's wrong.
除此之外又是什么导致肾功能障碍的呢
What causes kidney dysfunction on top of everything else?
砷中毒
Arsenic poisoning.
人是会变的
And people do change.
当我问兰德勒的过去时
Driscoll took it to heart
德里斯科尔很用心
when I asked him to think about Landon's history.
他变得很好  然后
He was much nicer, and then
这两个说不通
Wow, two ideas that don't make any sense.
如果是砷  他们应该上吐下泻
If it was arsenic, they'd be puking and pooping.
向陌生人说教
And conversations with moralizing strangers
不会改变他们的行为
do not make people change their behavior.
瑞秋肯定不会一而再的干这事了
Rachel is not gonna do that more than once.
低血糖会引发脑部  肾脏以及心脏问题
Whipple's could affect the brain, kidneys, heart.
但不会导致肠胃问题
Not without G.I. involvement.
你为何就不相信呢
Why is it impossible to believe
我的劝说很有说服力  他也...
I made a compelling argument, and he--
即便他改变了  也不会是因为你
If he changed, it's because something besides you
而是其他事情让他信服
made that argument compelling.
膀胱问题引起了继发性肾功能障碍
Compromised kidneys secondary to bladder issues
说明是由土壤中存在的肉毒素所导致的
points to botulism toxin, which lives in soil.
由男孩额头上的伤口
Got into the kid's bloodstream
进入其血管内
through the cut on his forehead.
由教官脚上的擦伤伤口
Got into the drill instructor's
也进入了他的血液里
through some abrasions on his feet.
有道理
Good idea.
给他俩都用上解毒剂
Give 'em both the antitoxin.
我瞧见了逃离这里的机会
I saw my chance to get out of here.
我得把握住机会
I had to take it.
不要找借口
Don't make excuses.
你偷了我的车钥匙
You tried to steal from me.
我告诉过你这帮孩子就这样
All these kids are manipulators.
绝对不能掉以轻心
You can't let your guard down.
你说"这帮孩子"是什么意思
What do you mean "All these kids"?
别把我和训练营里的那帮烂人混为一谈
Don't lump me in with the losers at that camp.
我看你和那里挺配的
Seems like you belong there.
这说不定是你唯一的出路
It may be your only chance.
听着  我是犯过错
Look, I've screwed up,
但我还没犯过法
but I've never been in trouble with the law.
你说你是因商店行窃而入训练营的
You said you were in for shoplifting.
店主在我
Store owner caught me
顺手牵零食时逮到了我
trying to boost some chips and stuff.
报告给了管理我的社工
Called my DCS caseworker.
我还以为营员都是因法院判决而入营的
I thought all the kids were there under court order.
一般而言是这样的
That's usually how it works.
为何他不一样呢
So why is he different?
我为何要照一张你的裸照呢
Why would I take a naked picture of you?
你是很有魅力  不过还没那么大魅力
You're cute, but you're not that cute.
现在请你离开
Now please go.
你是剩下唯一的嫌疑人了  我把你惹毛了
You're the only one left. You're pissed off.
我是很生气  因为你正在我的公寓里
I'm pissed off because you're in my apartment,
而我的男友很可能马上就过来了
and my boyfriend might be here any minute.
男友
Boyfriend.
我最不想做的事就是让他发现我出轨
Last thing I want to do is publicize that I cheated on him
所以我为何要让你出丑
so why would I prank you?
可婚礼那天你男友哪去了
And where was this boyfriend at the wedding?
-出城了  -真是便宜男友
- Out of town. - Conveniently.
这是上个月我姐姐生日会上的照片
It's from my sister's birthday last month.
在你狡辩他是我哥哥之前
And before you suggest he's my brother,
仔细看看  我和他是在热吻
note how I'm kissing him.
我们互惠互利  那是个错误
You used me, I used you. It was a mistake.
而我现在只想忘记过去
Now I just want to forget about it.
我刚刚和兰德勒的社工通了电话
I just got off the phone with Landon's DCS caseworker.
你说的对
You were right.
我的劝说本身并没让他信服
I'm not what made my argument compelling.
这是要去哪里
Where are we going?
给你的膀胱做次杀菌浴
To give your bladder an antibiotic wash
防止感染
to protect against infection.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是豪斯医生
I'm Dr. House.
那男孩和他妈妈简直是一个模子印出来的
And that boy is the spitting image of his mother.
当然  我从来没见过她本人
Of course, I've never seen her,
但分管他的社工告诉我的手下
but his care worker told my lackey
说是你替他付了参加训练营的费用
that you paid his enrolment fee at the camp.
这意味着你可能是他家人的朋友
That could mean that you're a family friend,
但若是这样  你何必匿名呢
but then, why hide it?
而唯一一个想要隐瞒的人...
The only person who'd want to hide it...
就是他不负责任的父亲
is his deadbeat dad,
而这个父亲决定要承担起父亲的职责
who has decided not to be a deadbeat anymore.
求求你  不要告诉他
Please, don't tell him.
我们费了好几天  找他俩之间的关系
We spend days looking for a link between them,
而他却不告诉我们这孩子是他的儿子
and he doesn't tell us the kid is his son.
我们一直在找共同的暴露源
We were looking for exposures.
他觉得这事和治疗没有关系
He didn't think it was medically relevant.
不久后  他也不用担心儿子发现真相了
Soon, he won't have to worry about his kidding finding out.
死了后  秘密就永远是秘密了
Being dead makes keeping secrets much easier.
肉毒素治疗对他们都不起作用
Neither one was responding to botulism treatment,
男孩已经开始出现痉挛了
And the boy started having seizures.
德里斯科尔也许是对的
And Driscoll might have been right
他们的父子关系是无关的
that their biological relationship doesn't matter.
遗传性疾病会在同一年龄段暴发
Genetic illness emerges when people are the same age,
但不会在同一周
not during the same week.
除非是由某种东西触发的
Unless there's a trigger.
环境因素可能
Genetic conditions can be set off
会抵消遗传因素
by things in the surroundings,
而明显地  这两人生活环境相同
and these two obviously share surroundings.
这种现象很罕见
That's a relatively rare phenomenon.
不过这正是我们的专长
Which is our specialty, I know.
我们的病人是亲属  不可能是巧合
Our patients are related. That can't be a coincidence.
我刚才灵光一闪
I just had an idea.
和我们的病例有关系吗
Relevant to our case?
没有
No.
老实坐下
Sit.
暴露于重金属可能会引起韦格纳肉芽肿
Wegener's can be brought on by exposure to heavy metals.
你们在营地发现什么没
Did you see anything at the camp?
在隔离房附近
Near the isolation hut,
有废旧的发电机电池
there were some old generator batteries.
会不会泄漏到了土壤中
Could have leaked into the soil?
但那样营地里的其他人
Seems like someone else in the camp
也会铅中毒
would have had lead poisoning.
你有更好的解释吗
You got anything better?
用环磷酰胺治疗
Treat with cyclophosphamide.
你去找你的灵光吧
Go find your bliss.
现在我要先离开了  我还有个约会
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a play date.
他妈妈去世时  你为何没站出来
Why didn't you step forward when his mom died?
我在她去世几个月后才知道
I found out she'd passed months later.
而那时  兰德勒已经被纳入领养系统了
By then, Landon was already in the foster system.
他出岔子时
I was figuring out a way to approach him
我正在想怎样才能进入他的生活
when he got into trouble,
所以我就把他带入训练营
so I brought him to the camp.
你要告诉他真相
You need to tell him.
我做不到  至少现在不行
I can't. Not now.
如果我死了  我留给他的唯一印象
If I die, the only thing I'll ever be to him
就是那个强迫他训练的混蛋教练
is the hardass who made him run obstacle courses.
你为了自己精神不受控状态下的行为
You'll apologize to me for something done
都会向我道歉
in a psychotic state,
怎么就不敢站出来  做个像样的父亲呢
but you won't own up to being his father.
不是说
What happened to
"男子汉要勇于承担责任"吗
"Actions have consequences, a man accepts them"?
我已经在他的生命中了
I'm in his life,
也正努力让他走上正途
and I am working to get him on the right path.
他需要的并不是位教官
He doesn't need a drill instructor.
而是位父亲
He needs a dad.
你能来真的很贴心
It's so sweet of you coming to this.
这不是为了支持你嘛
Just trying to be supportive.
听说这是男朋友的职责
I've heard that's what boyfriends do.
嗨  宝贝  玩的开心吗
Hi, honey. Hi. Did you have fun?
瑞秋玩的很开心  什么都会玩
Rachel had a great time. Played with everything.
真是个聪明的小姑娘
She's a very clever girl.
我抱歉要问些问题  有些家长
I'm sorry to ask this, but we've had some problems
会提前教孩子玩玩具
with parents coaching kids.
瑞秋异常快地学会了我们的玩具
Rachel caught onto our toys unusually quickly,
她甚至知道游戏叫做
And she even knew the game was called
"喂猴子"
"Feed the monkey."
虽然我很想让孩子来这儿上学
Uh, well, as eager as I am to have her go here,
我保证我绝对不会这么做
I promise you I would never do that.
瑞秋
Hey, Rachel.
你以前玩过"喂猴子"这个游戏吗
Have you ever played "Feed the monkey" before?
没有  妈妈
No, mama.
她看起来那么傻
She seemed so dumb.
但有压力时
But when the pressure was on,
她很清楚地知道该怎么做
she knew what had to be done,
做得还挺好
and she did it.
你这么焦虑是因为你家孩子撒谎了吗
You're pumped 'cause your kid lied?
不是我家孩子  她就是个小混蛋
She's not my kid. She's a pain in the ass.
而且她撒的谎可比你好多了
And she's a better liar than you are.
你不是上货车时划伤了腿
You didn't cut your leg getting into your truck.
伤口处有泥土和沙砾
The abrasion has dirt and gravel in it.
还有点肥料
A bit of fertilizer too.
摔在我的温室里了
Tripped in my greenhouse.
我在种自己的有机植物
Growing my own organic veggies.
别打听了  保密
Didn't ask. Not gonna tell.
她没犹豫迟疑  也没虚张声势
She didn't hesitate. She didn't oversell.
学会这样撒谎我用了很多年
Took me years to learn how to lie like that.
瑞秋却天生就会
And Rachel has it on instinct.
听起来你蛮喜欢那孩子嘛
Sounds like you're real fond of that kid.
你还真是"明察秋毫"
You're really not good with nuance, are you?
我欣赏的是她的天赋
I admire her talent.
让我先给你麻醉
I'm just gonna numb you up...
我得撤了
I gotta go.
最新的肾功能测试表明目前还没有改观
Latest kidney function test shows no improvement.
缝针很赞  疼吗
Nice stitches. Do they hurt?
不  他们给我打了点什么东西
No. They gave me a shot of something.
那叫做利多卡因[一种局部麻醉剂]
That was lidocaine.
它触发了一种遗传病
It triggered an underlying genetic condition
多样性卟啉病
Called variegate porphyria.
这可以解释他俩的病症
That would explain their symptoms.
我没打过利多卡因啊
But I didn't have any lidocaine.
托这个小魔王的福
But you had a handful of antihistamines,
你吃了不少抗组胺药
courtesy of the deviant in the next bed.
这也能触发卟啉病
It's also a porphyria trigger.
我们得了相同的遗传病吗
Wait, so we have the same genetic thing?
对
Yeah...
世界真小
Small world.
这是好消息
This is good news.
我们能用血色素控制病情
We can manage the condition with hematin.
做个肝脏移植你就痊愈了
A liver transplant could cure it.
我听说  两个病人可以共享一个捐赠肝脏
Sometimes two patients share one donated liver.
我们行吗
Would that work for us?
有可能
Possibly.
我们需要给你们验血  验组织类型
We'd have to test your blood, tissue type.
-如果匹配的话  -凭什么会匹配
- And if they matched-- - Why would they?
我们只是得了同一种病
Just because we have the same thing making us sick...
还有
Also...
我是你的亲生父亲
I'm your father.
我不信
I don't believe you.
你不信白人可以是坏爹
You don't think a white guy can be a bad father?
我很乐意为您验验DNA
Happy to check your DNA.
你认为如果他不是你爹他会这么说吗
Do you really think he'd say he's your dad if he isn't?
你又不是帅得惨绝人寰
It's not like you're a catch.
你太阴险了
You're evil.
你穿上衣服我都快认不出来了
Barely recognize you with your clothes on.
你和你妹妹都在婚礼上
You were at the wedding with your sister.
还跟她住一个屋
Shared a room with her too.
我去换鞋  然后
I came by to change my shoes, and...
在浴室看到你
I found you in the bathroom.
你这么久才找到我
It took you long enough to find me.
因为正常人都不会想到
Because when someone starts pranking you,
那个一直捉弄你的人是
the logical suspect is the overly protective sister
你床伴的过分护短的姐姐
of the woman you slept with once.
这和我妹妹无关
This has nothing to do with my sister.
那和什么有关
Then what does it have to do with?
如果你真的想不起来了
If you really have no clue,
那你太活该了
then you so deserve this.
你为了捉弄我
All that creativity and energy
花了那么多的时间精力
you put into pranking me...
肯定是想表达什么
It seems like you were trying to make a point.
你真不想告诉我是为什么吗
You really don't want to tell me what it was?
你超爱约翰·休斯的电影
You're a really big fan of John Hughes movies.
你难以理解地喜欢"妙不可言"
You inexplicably prefer some kind of wonderful
而不是"十六支蜡烛"  这很可能是因为
to sixteen candles, though that's probably because...
麦特森戴皮手套感觉很性感
Mary Stuart Masterson looked hot in those leather gloves.
我们招待会时聊天来着
We talked at the reception.
这是你恨我的原因  我们谈得很开心啊
That's why you hate me? It was fun.
确实很开心  直到我提到
It was great... until I mentioned that
第一次约会时我不会和男生上床
I don't sleep with guys on the first date.
你说你要去洗手间
And then you said you had to go to the bathroom,
就再也没回来
and you never came back.
恶有恶报
Actions have consequences.
你对每个混帐男人
Do you seek vengeance on every guy
都这么报复他吗
who acts like an ass?
你肯定忙得不可开交
Could be a full-time job.
我们聊天时  你看起来很不错
When we were talking, you seemed like a nice guy.
要不你就是一个伟大的演员
So either you're a great actor,
要不你就是只迷途的羔羊
or you're a nice guy who lost his way.
不管是什么原因
Whatever the reasons,
一点负强化都是必须的
a little negative reinforcement seemed to be warranted.
还有  你现在的密码是"大淫棍"
Oh, currently, your password is "Great big ho."
别在用"密码"当密码了
Change it back to anything but "Password."
对不起
Hey, I'm--I'm sorry.
为表达我的歉意  我请你吃晚饭吧
Let me prove it to you by taking you out to dinner.
不会立马就想和你上床
Followed by not sleeping with you.
我认真的
I'm serious.
你对你的生活不认真
Not on your life.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
没什么好谈的
Nothin' to say.
好吧
Okay.
我会等你准备好的
I'll wait till you're ready.
你是我儿子
You're my son.
我哪儿都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
等等
Wait a minute.
-这是什么  -小狗
- What is that? - A doggy.
-它怎么叫的  -汪
- What does it say? - Ruff!
对啦
That's right.
瓦尔登伍德打电话来了
Waldenwood called.
他们很喜欢瑞秋  但是没有名额了
They love Rachel, but they have no room.
都被兄弟姐妹占去了
Something about more siblings than usual.
让我们明年再申请
We should apply next year.
她很聪明  没问题的
She's a smart kid. She'll be fine.
你真这么想
You mean that?
嗯
Yeah, I do.